<resources>
    <string name="app_name">newsapp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="login_title">Login with one of the options</string>
    <string name="spaghetti_large_text">
        "Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook spaghetti in boiling water, stirring occasionally, until tender yet firm to the bite, about 12 minutes. Drain, toss spaghetti with 1 tablespoon olive oil, and set aside. \n\n"
        "Place diced bacon in a large skillet over medium heat; cook and stir until evenly browned, about 10 minutes. Drain bacon on paper towels, reserving 2 tablespoons bacon fat in the skillet. \n\n"
        "Add 1 tablespoon olive oil to bacon fat in the skillet. Add chopped onion and cook over medium heat until onion is translucent. Add minced garlic and cook until fragrant, about 1 minute. Add wine and cook 1 minute more. \n\n"
        "Return cooked bacon to the skillet; add cooked spaghetti. Toss to coat and heat through, adding more olive oil if it seems dry or sticks together. Add beaten eggs and cook, tossing constantly with tongs or a large fork, until eggs are barely set. Quickly add 1/2 cup Parmesan cheese and toss again. Season with salt and pepper (remember that bacon and Parmesan are very salty). \n\n"
        "Serve warm with chopped parsley sprinkled on top and extra Parmesan cheese at the table."
    </string>
    <string name="cinnamon_rolls_large_text">
        "Gather all ingredients and lightly grease 2 round cake pans with butter.\n\n"
        "Roll bread dough out to an 6x18-inch rectangle. Brush with melted butter\n\n"
        "Combine brown sugar, walnuts, and cinnamon in a small bowl; sprinkle over butter.\n\n"
        "Roll dough into a log, starting at the long edge. Moisten edge with water and seal.\n\n"
        "Cut log into 20 slices; arrange rolls, cut sides down, in prepared cake pans. Cover with a towel and let rise in a warm place until doubled in volume, about 90 minutes.\n\n"
        "Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Pour heavy cream over dough.\n\n"
        "Bake in preheated oven until golden brown, about 25 minutes.\n\n"
        "Mix confectioners' sugar, milk, and vanilla extract in a small bowl; drizzle over warm cinnamon rolls to serve.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="fluffy_scrambled_large_text">
        "Whisk eggs with salt until completely combined and very foamy.\n\n"
        "Melt butter in a skillet over low heat until bubbling. Add whisked eggs; cook, stirring frequently for even, moist curds, until thickened and creamy, but still shiny, 2 to 3 minutes.\n\n"
        "Remove scrambled eggs from the pan before they begin to look dry, as they will continue to thicken off the heat.\n\n"
        "Variation: Saute 1/4 cup chopped bell pepper and 1/4 cup chopped mushrooms in 1 tablespoon olive oil until soft, about 5 minutes. Stir into eggs just before serving.\n\n"
        "You can add blistered tomatoes and shredded aged and/or soft cheeses to this if you like; add just before serving\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="mayo_chicken_large_text">
        "Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).\n\n"
        "Place chicken pieces into a 9x13-inch baking dish. Stir together mayonnaise, garlic, rosemary, salt, and black pepper in a bowl. Spread mayonnaise mixture over chicken; top with Parmesan cheese.\n\n"
        "Bake in the preheated oven until no longer pink in the center and the juices run clear, about 1 hour and 10 minutes. An instant-read thermometer inserted into the center should read at least 165 degrees F (74 degrees C).\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="marzetti_large_text">
        "Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Lightly grease a 7x11-inch casserole dish with cooking spray.\n\n"
        "Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Add rotini and cook until tender yet firm to the bite, 6 to 8 minutes; drain. Run cold water over pasta to stop it from cooking further.\n\n"
        "While the pasta is cooking, cook ground beef and sausage in a large skillet over medium-high heat until completely browned and crumbly, 7 to 10 minutes. Add onion, celery, garlic, and bell pepper; cook and stir until vegetables are tender, about 5 minutes. Season with salt and pepper. Remove from the heat and stir in tomato sauce and diced tomatoes. Let cool for 5 minutes.\n\n"
        "Spread pasta over the bottom of the prepared baking dish. Sprinkle Italian cheese blend over rotini, then pour meat sauce over top. Cover the dish with heavy-duty aluminum foil.\n\n"
        "Bake in the preheated oven for 45 minutes. Remove the foil and sprinkle Cheddar cheese over the casserole. Continue to bake until Cheddar has melted, about 5 minutes. Rest for 10 minutes before serving.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="kalbi_large_text">
        "Stir together soy sauce, brown sugar, water, green onions, garlic, and sesame oil in a bowl until sugar has dissolved\n\n"
        "Place ribs in a large resealable plastic bag. Pour marinade over ribs. Seal the bag and refrigerate for 3 hours to overnight\n\n"
        "Preheat an outdoor grill for medium-high heat; lightly oil the grate\n\n"
        "Remove ribs from the bag; shake off excess marinade and discard marinade. Grill ribs on the preheated grill until meat is still pink but not bloody nearest the bone, 5 to 7 minutes per side.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="korean_bbq_large_text">
        "Place ribs in a large pot and cover with cold water. Soak ribs in the refrigerator for 1 hour to pull out any blood. Drain\n\n"
        "Combine Asian pear, onion, and garlic in a blender; blend until smooth. Pour into a large bowl and stir in soy sauce, brown sugar, honey, sesame oil, and black pepper. Add ribs to soy mixture; turn to coat evenly. Cover the bowl and marinate in the refrigerator, 8 hours to overnight.\n\n"
        "Preheat an outdoor grill for high heat and lightly oil the grate\n\n"
        "Remove ribs from marinade and cook on the preheated grill until meat is tender and the outside is crusty, 5 to 10 minutes per side. Discard marinade.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="gyro_bbq_large_text">
        "Pulse onion in a food processor until finely chopped. Scoop onions onto the center of a towel, gather up the towel ends, and squeeze to remove liquid\n\n"
        "Combine onions, lamb, beef, garlic, oregano, cumin, marjoram, rosemary, thyme, pepper, and salt in a large bowl. Mix with your hands until well combined. Cover and refrigerate 1 to 2 hours to allow the flavors to blend\n\n"
        "Preheat the oven to 325 degrees F (165 degrees C).\n\n"
        "Place the meat mixture into a food processor and pulse until finely chopped and the texture feels tacky, about 1 minute. Transfer to a 7x4-inch loaf pan, and pack down to make sure there are no air pockets.\n\n"
        "Line a large roasting pan with a damp kitchen towel. Place the loaf pan in the center of the towel-lined roasting pan, and transfer it into the preheated oven. Carefully pour boiling water into the roasting pan until it comes halfway up the sides of the loaf pan.\n\n"
        "Bake in the preheated oven until gyro meat is no longer pink in the center, about 45 minutes to 1 hour. An instant-read thermometer inserted into the center should read at least 160 degrees F (70 degrees C).\n\n"
        "Pour off any accumulated fat, and allow to cool slightly before slicing thinly and serving.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="burge_large_text">
        "Preheat an outdoor grill for medium heat and lightly oil the grate\n\n"
        "Mix ground lamb, garlic powder, rosemary, thyme, salt, and pepper together in a large bowl until thoroughly combined.\n\n"
        "Shape mixture into 4 patties\n\n"
        "Place patties on the preheated grill and cook until firm and slightly pink in the center, about 5 minutes per side. An instant-read thermometer inserted into the center should read 140 degrees F (60 degrees C). Alternately, you can cook the patties to your desired degree of doneness. Rest patties while assembling toppings.\n\n"
        "Mix mayonnaise and mustard together in a small bowl\n\n"
        "Spread 1 tablespoon on bottom of each hamburger bun; top each one with a lamb patty, tomato slice, and some greens. Sandwich with top bun to serve\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="lamb_stew_large_text">
        "Heat oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat. Add lamb and onions; cook and stir until lamb is browned and onions are starting to soften, about 5 minutes. Transfer lamb mixture to a slow cooker\n\n"
        "Add potatoes, carrots, celery, and mushrooms. Stir in beef broth, tomato paste, beer, Worcestershire sauce, rosemary, salt, and pepper; cover.\n\n""Cook on High for 7 hours. Add peas and cook for an additional 15 minutes. Season with salt and pepper.\n\n"

    </string>


    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>

</resources>